Preliminary Guide to the Luther Brady papers, MS2147.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- UP0026 (Box 26)
  - 1st World Conference in Head & Neck Oncology, Madrid, Spain, 12/3-6/98 (Felipe A. Calvo, MD), 12/03/1998 - 12/06/1998 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - I World Congress on Head and Neck Oncology, Madrid, Spain (F. Calvo, MD), 11/29/98-12/3/98, 11/29/1998 - 12/03/1998 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Loyola University Medical Center, Maywood, IL, 11/18/98 (B. Emami, MD), 11/18/1998 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Modern Radiotherapy, Allowed Technologies & Optimized Management, Rome, Italy, 11/9-13/98 (Prof. Numa Cellini), 11/09/1998 - 11/13/1998 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Slides for ASTRO Refresher Course, 10/25-29/98, Phoenix, AZ, 10/25/1998 - 10/29/1998 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- UP0027 (Box 27)
  - GWU Leadership Weekend, 6/17/00, Lansdowne, 06/17/2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Jamea Catalano / Frederick Campbell-- 6/9/2000, 06/09/2000 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - GWU Board Retreat: 6/16-18/2000, GWU Leadership Weekend: 6/16-18/2000, Landsdowne Resort, Leesburg, VA, 06/16/2000 - 06/18/2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Charleston, SC, 05/25/2000 - 05/29/2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Philadelphia County Medical Society, Strittmatter Award Committee Mtg., 5/24/2000, 12 Noon (Brokke Roberts, MD), 05/24/2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Radiological Society 85th Annual Meeting, Hershey, PA, 05/20/2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - American Society of Clinical Oncology, New Orleans, LA, 5/20-23/2000 - Editorial Bd. Mtg. AJCO, 5/23, 05/20/2000 - 05/23/2000 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - GWU Board of Trustees Mtg./Committee Mtgs., 5/18-19/2000, Washington, DC, 05/18/2000 - 05/19/2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - American Board of Radiology Oral Bds., 5/13-16/2000, Louisville, KY, 05/13/2000 - 05/16/2000 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Professor at Medical College of Virginia/VCU, Richmond, VA, 5/10-12/2000 (R.K. Schmidt-Ullrich, MD), 05/10/2000 - 05/12/2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - ACRO 10th Annual Meeting, Park Hyatt Washington, Washington, DC, 05/06/2000 - 05/07/2000 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Delaware Breast Cancer Coalition 2nd Annual Breast Ca Symposium, 4/26/00, DuPont Country Club, Wilmington, 04/26/2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - 4/25/2000--Northeast Regional Cancer Institute (NRCI) Board of Directors Mtg., Marian Community Hospital, By-Laws, 04/25/2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn. Board of Trustees Meeting. 4/17-18/00, RSNA Bldg., Oak Brook, IL, 04/17/2000 - 04/18/2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - University of Turku, Turku, Finland, 4/6-9/2000 (Prof. Eeva Nordman), 04/06/2000 - 04/09/2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Karolinska sjukhuset - Radiumhemmet, Stockholm, Sweden (Dr. Ulrik Ringborg), 04/09/2000- 04/11/2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Prof. H.-P. Heilmann's Retirement/Scientific Symposium, Hamburg, Germany, 03/18/2000 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Springer's Medical Radiology-Radiation Oncology Series Editor Meeting, 3/16/2000, Heidelberg, Germany, 03/16/2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - GWU Committee & Board Meetings--2/10-11/2000, Washington, DC, 02/10/2000 - 02/11/2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - 12/25-30/99 Daytona Beach, FL, 12/25/1999 - 12/30/1999 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - RSNA 85th Scientific Assembly & Annual Meeting, 11/28-12/3/99, McCormick Place, Chicago, IL, 11/28/1999 - 12/03/1999 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Madrid, Spain, 11/10/1999 - 11/17/1999 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Samuel S. Fleisher Art Memorial honoring Dene Louchheim commissioned from Sam Maitin, 11/08/1999 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Orlando, Florida, 11/06/1999 - 11/07/1999 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - The Phila. County Medical Society 150th Anniv. & Awards Program-- L.W.B. Strittmatter Award, 11/05/1999 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - ASTRO, San Antonio Convention Ctr., San Antonio, TX, 10/31/1999 - 11/03/1999 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- UP0028 (Box 28)
  - Visiting Professor at USC School of Medicine, Dept. Rad. Onc., 12/12-16/2001 (Z. Petrovich, M.D.), 12/12/2001 - 12/16/2001 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Restaurant Alex, Los Angeles, CA, 12/12/2001, 7 pm (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia-- Development Committee Mtg., 11/8/01, 4 pm, Gross Library, 11/08/2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - FNIH Board of Directors Mtg., 11/7/2001, Washington, DC, 11/07/2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - CDOC Board Meeting, KGH of Bayhealth Medical Center-- Board Room 10/25/2001, 3:00 pm (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - College of Physicians of Phila. Com. on Administration, Mitchell Hall reception & mtg., 10/22/01, 4:30 pm (RE Campbell), 10/22/2001 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - FNIH 50th Anniversary Symposium Exec. Committee, etc, Brain Research, Library of Congress, Washington, DC, 10/9/2001, 10/09/2001 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - CIM Major Gifts Committee, Bok Room, 9/26/2001, 11:30-1:30 pm, Mtg./Lunch, 09/26/2001 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Bayhealth 2001 Board Planning Retreat, Boardwalk Plaza Hotel Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, 9/28-29/2001, 09/28/2001 - 09/29/2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - RSNA R&E Foundation Board of Trustees & Fund Development Committee Mtgs., 9/12-14/2001, Sonoma Mission Inn, CA, 09/12/2001 - 09/14/2001 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - London: 9/1-6/01, Belin: 9/6-9/01, 09/01/2001 - 09/09/2001 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - ASTRO Fundraising (Drs Hussey/Donaldson)--Interview, Mary Elizabeth McKeon, 8/14/01. 2:30 pm, 08/14/2001 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Santa Fe, NM - 7/29-8/11/2001, 07/29/2001 - 08/11/2001 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Fernheim Farm - 100th Anniversary 7/21/2001 (William S. Newlin, Nancy & Lisa), 07/21/2001 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Cooperstown, NY; Glimmerglass, Sharon Hghts, 7/13-15/2001 (Dr. Joe Barthoed), 07/13/2001 - 07/15/2001 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - John Edward Porter Neuroscience Research Center at the NIH (6/22/01), 06/22/2001 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - GWU Board of Trustees Retreat, Four Seasons Hotel, Georgetown, 6/22 & 23/2001, 06/22/2001 - 06/23/2001 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - ABR Oral Examinations, Louisville, KY, 6/9/2001: Orientation, 6/10-11/2001: Examinations, 06/09/2001 - 06/11/2001 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Women's Cancer Research Association (WCRA) Luncheon, Sun., 6/3/01. 11:30 am, Radisson Hotel, US 1 & Old Lincoln Hghwy., 06/03/2001 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Symposium in Honor of Dr. C.A. Perez's Retirement, Washington University, St. Louis, MO, 5/31-6/2/2001, 05/31/2001 - 06/02/2001 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Deutscher Rontgenkongress, Weisbaden, Germany, 5/23-26/2001, 05/23/2001 - 05/26/2001 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Springer Verlag, Heidelberg, Germany & Dinner Honoring Prof. F. Heuck 5/20-23/2001 (Ursula Davis), 05/20/2001 - 05/23/2001 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - IV Course of simulation & planning in External Radiotherapy, Madrid, Spain, 5/24-25/2001, Hosp Gen Univ. Gregorio Maranon, 05/24/2001 - 05/25/2001 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - London, England, 5/16-20/2001, 05/16/2001 - 05/20/2001 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - GWU Bd. of Trustees Mtg: 5/17-18/01, Commencement: 5/17-19 & 27/01, regretted, 05/17/2001 - 05/27/2001 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - PMA 125th Anniversary of its Founding, 5/10/2001, Sir Howard Hodgkin exhibit, & PAFA Commencement, Sir Howard speaker 5/11, 05/10/2001 - 05/11/2001 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Radiotherapy of Benign Disease Annual Mtg., DEGRO, Essen, 5/4-5/2001, Alfred Krupp Krankenhaus (Seegenschmiedt & Prof/ Makoski), 05/04/2001 - 05/05/2001 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - ACRO 11th Annual Meeting, Loews Santa Monica Beach Hotel, 5/4-6/2001, Santa Monica, CA, 05/04/2001 -05/06/2001 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Memorial Service for Mrs. Henriette Baum in New York City, 04/18/2001 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Lecture to students at MCP, Auditorium B: "Introduction to Radiation Therapy", 04/16/2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - RSNA Fund Development Com. Special Mtg., RSNA Headquarters, Oak Brook, IL, 03/29/2001 - 03/30/2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Foundation for the NIH Board of Directors Mtg., NIH campus, Bldg. 60, 03/27/2001 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, Committee on Administration, 03/06/2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- UP0029 (Box 29)
  - RSNA- Correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - RSNA R/E Foundation Fundraising info (5/99), 05/1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - RSNA R&E Fndn. Appointments, 11/1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Dr. & Mrs. Philip Rubin's 50th Wedding Anniversary, 8/30/02 - 9/1/02, Rochester, NY, 08/30/2002 - 09/01/2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia Committee on Development Mtg., 7/24/2002, 07/24/2002 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - CIM Season Premiere Gala Committee Chairs Mtg., Bok Rm, Lunch served., 06/26/2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - ABR Dedication of new office Building, Tucson, AZ (R.R. Hattery, MD/ Trusteees), 10/13/2001 - 10/14/2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 2002 Vacation, Santa Fe, NM, 07/27/2002 - 08/14/2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - PMA Board of Trustees Mtg., Seminar Rm., 06/20/2002 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - NCI Telephone Conference Call for Review of Dr. Dennis Leeper's Revised Application, 6/18/02, 1 pm (R. Bramhall, PhD), 06/18/2002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - CIM Board of Trustees Meeting, Field Concert Hall, 3:30 pm, 6/13/2002, 06/13/2002 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - RTOG Semi-Annual Meeting, Loews Hotel, Phila., PA, 6/13-16/02, 06/13/2002 - 06/16/2002 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - College of Physicians Planning Com., Lewis & Clark Exhibition Gala Luncheon Mtg., 06/11/2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - PMA Board of Trustees hosting a Meet the Chairman Breakfast to introduce Gerry Lenfest, 06/06/2002 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - CDOC Board Meeting, Kent General Hosp., Dover, DE, 06/04/2002 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - FNIH Board of Directors Mtg., at Hogan & Hartson, Washington, DC, 05/31/2002 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 7th Intern'l Mtg. on Progress in Radio-Oncology, Salzburg, Austria (Prof. H.D. Kogelnik), 05/15/2002 - 05/19/2002 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Juan del Regato 2002 Lecture/Gold Medal Presentation, Dinner, Harbor Ct. Hotel, 5/6/02, 7:30 pm, Baltimore, MD, regretted, 05/06/2002 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - ACRO Annual Meeting, Park Hyatt, Washington, DC, 05/03/2002 - 05/05/2002 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - CDOC Board of Directors Mtg., KGH, Board Room, 3:30 pm, 5/1/2002, Dover, DE, 05/01/2002 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - EMD Pharmaceuticals Mtg., Room 4105 NCB, HUH, Philadelphia, PA, 5/1/2002 (Dr. Grant, Linda Goldman), 05/01/2002 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - ARS 84th Annual Mtg., 4/27-5/1/2002, Las Croabas, Puerto Rico, 04/27/2002 - 05/01/2002 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn. Bd. of Trustees Mtg., Pointe South Mountain Resort, Phoenix, AZ, 04/15/2002 - 04/17/2002 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Video/Interview with Dr. Carl Mansfield, Univ. of Maryland, Baltimore, MD, 04/11/2002 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - The Phillips Collection Dinner with Guest, John Walker, Washington, DC, 04/09/2002 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia Committee on Administration, 4/8/2002, 4:30 pm (R.E. Campbell, MD, Chr), 04/08/2002 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Siloam Ministries Art Exhibition and Auction--Art & Soul (Fr. Don Reilly), 04/07/2002 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Phila. County Medical Society, Strittmatter Award Committee Mtg., 04/01/2002 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - CDOC Board of Directors Annual Mtg., KGH Board Rm., 3/27/02, 3 pm, Dover, DE, 03/27/2002 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - GWU - Dedication of Univ. Art Gallery in School of Public Affairs & Public Media, 03/25/2002 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Mr. Allan Grobman, West Palm Beach, FL, 03/15/2002 - 03/17/2002 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - CIM Board of Trustees Meeting, 03/14/2002 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - 10th Annual Medical Dosimetry/Physics Symposium, Doubletree Hotel, Phila., 03/07/2002 - 03/10/2002 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Colorectal Cancer Symposium, Wyndham Franklin Plaza (Michael Buckmire, MD), 03/05/2002 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - GWU Medical Center Committee Mtg., Washington, DC- Ross Hall, 02/07/2002 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - CDOC Board Meeting, KGH Board Room, 01/31/2002 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - LSU Site Visit - External Review, Dept. Radiation Oncology, New Orleans, LA, 10/30/2001 - 11/01/2001 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Daytona Beach, FL, 07/02/2001 - 07/08/2001 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- UP0030 (Box 30)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1:30 pm, 10/12/04: Committee on Development; 3-5 pm, 10/12/04: Board of Trustees, 10/12/2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Daytona Beach, FL, 08/28/2003 - 09/01/2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - EMD Pharmaceuticals Mtg., Marriott Hotel, Phila, 08/22/2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Lord and Lady Soulsby, Union League, 08/20/2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Summer 7/24-8/13/2003, Santa Fe, NM, 07/24/2003 - 08/13/2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Santa Fe, NM, 06/26/2003 - 07/05/2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sundaravej, Kunthon, MD, MSc, 6/21/2003, Sat., Eugene P. Pendergrass Program, HUP, 06/21/2003 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - WCRA Luncheon--Officers ar about 11 am, Physick House, 06/07/2003 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - CDOC Board of Directors Mtg. in Board Rm. at KGH, 06/05/2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Fleisher's Annual Founders Award, 06/02/2003 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Phillips Collection Annual Board of Trustees Mtg. & Retreat, Middleburg, VA, 05/31/2003 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - ASCO Annual Mtg., Hyatt McCormick Place in Chicago, IL (History of ASCO), 06/01/2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - PMA East Asian Art Committee, Committee Room, 05/29/2003 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Boston, MA, 05/24/2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Fleisher Board of Directors Mtg. (budget), 05/20/2003 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - PMA Committee Mtg. on Prints, Drawings, and Photographs in Perelman Bldg., 05/20/2003 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - The Phillips Collecion exhibition of works by Howard Hodgkin, Wash., DC, 05/18/2002 - 07/18/2002 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - ACR Annual Mtg., Washington Hilton & Towers, Washington, DC, 05/10/2003 - 05/15/2003 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Dinner re Art Program at Catholic Universities at Washington Square, 05/07/2003 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - College of Physicians Development Committee Mtg., Gross Library, 05/07/2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Chateau d'Artigny, Montbazon, France, 04/18/2003 - 04/26/2003 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - ARS, Paris, France - Intercontinental Hotel, 04/26/2003 - 04/30/2003 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Daytona Beach, FL, 04/24/2003 - 04/30/2003 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - CIM Board of Trustees Meeting in Studio IIJ, 04/23/2003 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Phila. County Medical Society Strittmatter Award Committee Mtg., 04/10/2003 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Phila. Antiques Show--Historical Blue Staffordshire of Phila., U of PA Med.Ctr., 04/04/2003 - 04/09/2003 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - RSNA Research and Education Fdn., Palmer House Hotel, Chicago, IL, 04/02/2003 - 04/04/2003 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Colonial Dames, 03/19/2003 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - ACRO 2003 Meeting, Tapatio Cliffs Resort, Phoenix, AZ, 02/27/2003 - 03/02/2003 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - PMA Board of Trustees Mtg. in Ruth & Raymond G. Perelman Bldg., 02/20/2003 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Christmas/New Years - 2002-2003, Daytona Beach, FL., 12/23/2002 - 01/02/2003 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Spring Valley Editorial Board Mtg., Heidelberg, Germany, 12/16/2002 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - National Royal Academy of Medicine, Madrid, Spain (Prof. F.A. Calvo), 12/12/2002 - 12/13/2002 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - 16th Annual Simon Kramer Lecture & Memorial Service, 12/09/2002 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - PMA Executive Committee Mtg., 11/21/2002 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn., and Annual Meeting, Chicago, IL, 11/29/2002 - 12/06/2002 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - ACRO Board of Chancellors Mtg., 11/08/2002 - 11/10/2002 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - CIM Symphony Season Premiere Gala, Alma Cohen/LWB-Co-Chair, 10/21/2002 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, Committee on Administration, 10/21/2002 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - PMA Annual Mtg., Organizational Mtg., & Board of Trustees Mtg., 10/17/2002 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Cancer Mtg., Pisa-San Romano, Italy: 9/30-10/1/02, 4th Int'l Congress, Bioengineering; 10/1-2/02, 7th Int'l Congress, Mgmt. Malignancies, 09/30/2002 - 10/02/2002 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn., Bd. of Trustees Mtg. Dinner with Bd. Dir., Palmer House, Chicago, IL, 09/19/2002 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Inn at Stonington, Stonington Village, Stonington, CT, 08/23/2002 - 08/25/2002 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - College of Physicians of Phila.--Visit from Dame Deirdre Hine, Dr. Anne Grocock, Roy.Soc.Med., 01/29/2002 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, Committee on Development Mtg., 01/10/2002 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- UP0031 (Box 31)
  - Lord Lawson Soulsby, House of Lords, London, England, 02/28/2001 - 03/04/2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Hearing in Office of Attorney General, 1/29/2001, Pittsburgh, PA re AHERF, 01/29/2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Germany: 1/12-21/2001, Frankfurt / Cologne / Stuttgart, 01/12/2001 - 01/21/2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Christmas 2000 - Santa Fe, NM, 12/23/2000 - 12/28/2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 12/16/2000, Saturday, 10:30 am, National Cathedral, Cosmos Club, Washington, DC (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - RSNA Research & Education Fdn., Bd. of Trustees Mtg., 11/26-12/1/00, McCormick Place, Chicago, IL, 11/26/2000 - 12/01/2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Lady Caroline Simmonds & Tara, 11/17/2000 - 11/18/2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Colgate Today Program, Hamilton, NY, 11/09/2000 - 11/11/2000 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - ASTRO 42nd Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 10/22/2000 - 10/26/2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - GWU Committee Mtgs., Washington, DC, 10/19/2000 - 10/20/2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - ACRO Board of Chancellors Mtg., Venetian Hotel, Las Vagas, NV (Robert Kagan, MD), 10/14/2000 - 10/15/2000 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - CANCER Editorial Advisory Board Mtg., NY, NY, 10/12/2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Vascular Endothelium, Basic/Clin. Aspects, 3rd Intern'l Congress, 10/2-3/2000, Pisa (Prof. Angelo Carpi), 10/02/2000 - 10/03/2000 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - American College of Radiology Annual Mtg. 2000, 9/23-27/2000, Hilton NY, 09/23/2000 - 09/27/2000 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - RSNA Research & Education Foundation Consensus Conference, Oak Brook, IL, 08/26/2000 - 08/27/2000 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Constance Battle, MD, NIH Fdn., NCI, Bldg. 60, Cloister Ct., Georgetown Rd., Center Dr., Bethesda, MD, 08/18/2000 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Santa Fe, NM, 07/29/2000 - 08/12/2000 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- UP0032 (Box 32)
  Many unlabeled folders and loose papers, most relating to George Washington University Alumni Association and Board of Trustees.
  - GWU Partnership Board Meeting, 10/28/97, Washington, DC (Lou Katz's Office: 2121 Eye St, NW, Suite 701), 10/28/1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - GWU Committee Mtgs. - 10/30/97, GWU Board of Trustees Mtg. - 10/31/97, Washington, DC, 10/30/1997 - 10/31/1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - GWU 50th Reunion, Washington, DC, 9/27/96, 09/27/1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - GWU Centuries Campaign Steering Committee, 10/1/96, 12 n - 2 pm, Elliott Rm, Marvin Center (Oliver T. Carr, Jr., Chair), 10/01/1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)